<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview on CoLD Tech Wiki</title>
    <link>//localhost:45893/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview on CoLD Tech Wiki</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:45893/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Post 3</title>
      <link>//localhost:45893/posts/post-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 11:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:45893/posts/post-3/</guid>
      <description>Occaecat aliqua consequat laborum ut ex aute aliqua culpa quis irure esse magna dolore quis. Proident fugiat labore eu laboris officia Lorem enim. Ipsum occaecat cillum ut tempor id sint aliqua incididunt nisi incididunt reprehenderit. Voluptate ad minim sint est aute aliquip esse occaecat tempor officia qui sunt. Aute ex ipsum id ut in est velit est laborum incididunt. Aliqua qui id do esse sunt eiusmod id deserunt eu nostrud aute sit ipsum.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 2</title>
      <link>//localhost:45893/posts/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:45893/posts/post-2/</guid>
      <description>Anim eiusmod irure incididunt sint cupidatat. Incididunt irure irure irure nisi ipsum do ut quis fugiat consectetur proident cupidatat incididunt cillum. Dolore voluptate occaecat qui mollit laborum ullamco et. Ipsum laboris officia anim laboris culpa eiusmod ex magna ex cupidatat anim ipsum aute. Mollit aliquip occaecat qui sunt velit ut cupidatat reprehenderit enim sunt laborum. Velit veniam in officia nulla adipisicing ut duis officia.&#xA;Exercitation voluptate irure in irure tempor mollit Lorem nostrud ad officia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Post 1</title>
      <link>//localhost:45893/posts/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:45893/posts/post-1/</guid>
      <description>Tempor proident minim aliquip reprehenderit dolor et ad anim Lorem duis sint eiusmod. Labore ut ea duis dolor. Incididunt consectetur proident qui occaecat incididunt do nisi Lorem. Tempor do laborum elit laboris excepteur eiusmod do. Eiusmod nisi excepteur ut amet pariatur adipisicing Lorem.&#xA;Occaecat nulla excepteur dolore excepteur duis eiusmod ullamco officia anim in voluptate ea occaecat officia. Cillum sint esse velit ea officia minim fugiat. Elit ea esse id aliquip pariatur cupidatat id duis minim incididunt ea ea.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Data Structure and Management</title>
      <link>//localhost:45893/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:45893/data/</guid>
      <description>Data Structure and Management Database Structure The database is organized into multiple related tables that store different types of legal information:&#xA;Main Data Tables Answers (14,942 records) HCCH Answers (20 records) Domestic Instruments (195 records) Domestic Legal Provisions (99 records) Regional Instruments (6 records) Regional Legal Provisions (129 records) International Instruments (1 record) International Legal Provisions (22 records) Court Decisions (1,321 records) Arbitral Institutions (28 records) Arbitral Rules (28 records) Arbitral Awards (67 records) Literature (217 records) Metadata Tables Themes (15 records) Questions (61 records) Jurisdictions (249 records) Topics (0 records) Glossary (29 records) Abbreviations (60 records) Specialists (68 records) Airtable Configuration Components Base: Collection of all data tables Table: Individual data tables within the base Field: Columns within tables (various data types) Record: Individual rows within tables Views: Saved configurations of filtered, sorted, or grouped data Naming Conventions Table and Field names follow title case capitalization per APA guidelines &amp;ldquo;Linked&amp;rdquo; columns are named &amp;lt;TABLE NAME&amp;gt; &amp;quot;Link&amp;quot; Lookup columns are named &amp;lt;TABLE NAME&amp;gt; &amp;lt;COLUMN NAME&amp;gt; Data Entry Rules For Answers/Questions/Jurisdictions Tables Use search/filter/group functions to locate records Edit existing fields as needed Do not add new entries to these tables For answers, select from predefined dropdown options For Legal Provisions/Court Decisions/Arbitral Awards Tables Add new records as needed Edit existing information directly in the relevant fields For Concepts Edit existing fields Use &amp;ldquo;Assignee&amp;rdquo; column to define responsibilities File Storage In addition to structured data in Airtable:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deployment Guide</title>
      <link>//localhost:45893/deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:45893/deployment/</guid>
      <description>Deployment Guide Production Environment The COLD platform is deployed using Microsoft Azure services:&#xA;Web Application: Accessible at https://www.cold.global Database: PostgreSQL instance on Azure Container Orchestration: Azure Kubernetes Service Application Hosting: Azure Container Apps Deployment Process While specific deployment processes are not detailed in the data management plan, the following general workflow can be inferred:&#xA;Data is maintained in Airtable Selected data is synchronized to the PostgreSQL database Web application containers are deployed to Azure Updates to the web application are managed through Azure&amp;rsquo;s deployment tools Backup Procedures Regular backup procedures have been established:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>System Architecture</title>
      <link>//localhost:45893/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:45893/architecture/</guid>
      <description>System Architecture Overall Architecture The COLD platform uses a multi-tier architecture:&#xA;Data Layer:&#xA;Primary data storage in Airtable cloud database PostgreSQL database for the public-facing web application Application Layer:&#xA;API interface to Airtable for data management Custom web application for public access Container-based microservices for specific functionality Presentation Layer:&#xA;Web interface accessible at cold.global Administrative interface for research team Database Architecture The system uses a relational database model with multiple interconnected tables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Technology Stack</title>
      <link>//localhost:45893/stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:45893/stack/</guid>
      <description>Technology Stack Database Technologies Primary Data Storage Airtable Plus Plan subscription Capacity for ~15,000 records per base 5GB attachment storage per base Relational database structure Cloud-synced with Amazon Web Services infrastructure Secondary Database PostgreSQL on Azure Stores data for public web interface Synchronized with selected Airtable data Cloud Infrastructure Microsoft Azure Azure Container Apps: Hosts containerized application components Azure Kubernetes Service: Orchestrates containers for scalability Azure PostgreSQL: Managed database service Development Tools Airtable API: For programmatic access to database content Airtable Scripting Extension: For metadata collection and automation Backup Tools SwitchDrive: University-provided cloud storage OneDrive: Secondary backup location CSV Export: Data format for backups Security &amp;amp; Compliance Airtable Security Features: ISO/IEC 27001:2013 certification SOC 2 compliance GDPR compliance Web Application Public-facing website: https://www.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
